Richard Morris

Full Stack Web Developer

(770) 361-9768 rallanmorris@gmail.com Atlanta, GA Motivated Computer Science graduate from the University of Georgia with I year's experience in Software Development. Excited to utilize my skill set in JavaScript, Python, and Web Development to achieve lasting impacts on user experience.

Portfolio Github LinkedIn

Skills:

- Python and Django Web Framework
- JavaScript
- HTML/CSS
- Git
- SQLite
- Self-Motivated and flexible
- Strong teamwork and communication skills
- Creative Thinking

Education:

University of Georgia

BS Computer Science

Relevant Coursework:

Data Structures; Software

Engineering; Software Development;

Web Programming; Systems

Programming

Portfolio Projects: (Website)

Super Snake (Link)

 A new take on a classic arcade game written in Python using Pygame

Apnea Trainer (Link)

 Hold your breath longer using the science of Apnea Tables.
Written in Javascript/HTML

Work Experience:

Botanical Gardens / Atlanta, GA

Nov 2022 - May 2023

Event Operations Associate

 Worked together with a team to manage events and correspond with clients.

Strike Tennis / Kennesaw, GA

March 2020 - Oct 2022

Assistant Coach

- Taught students and trained junior coaches in after school programs.
- Strike Tennis teaches tennis to over 400 students in 10 different schools.

Thrive Technologies / Kennesaw, GA

January 2020 - August 2020

Software Development Intern

- Worked both solo and with a team using the Kanban framework.
- Developed new features (such as bulk import of SKUs) and fixed bugs in the web application.
- Maintained SQL Servers
- Corresponded with customers

UGA Sustainability / Athens, GA

Summer 2019

Software Development Internship

- Worked with a 3 person team over the summer to create an educational web application to teach students about recycling.
- Used Javascript, HTML, and Heroku.